What's the current situation?
We're tracking three Savages.
There's damage to the Zwei Island city block.
Evacuation of citizens is nearly complete.
Hayato-sama! Emile-sama!
Mei-Mai? What are you doing here?
I'm working.
Chris-sama, you should take your post, too.
Roger that.
Chris-sama is the main analyst here.
Main analyst?
But isn't he in middle school?
Forget your average middle or high schooler,
his brains and skills put him above even
Warslarn HQ's intelligence division.
He truly belongs here.
Wow.
I'm honored.
We have visual on the third Savage.
Putting it on the main screen.
It's huge.
A giant.
It's a Trenta-class.
Its estimated ability values are unknown.
We have to deal with one of those...
Claire-sama, prepare to sortie.
On second thought, Charlotte Dimandius,
I'm going to pass on deploying Emile Crossfode
and Kisaragi Hayato today.
They may have your recommendation,
but they have zero experience
out in the field.
Dealing with a normal Savage
would be one thing,
but a Trenta-class is too much
for them to handle.
So what's your plan?
Are the three of you going to
head out by yourselves?
In a few hours, a Warslarn HQ
support team will arrive,
so if we can just hold out until then...
Oh?
I never thought you would depend on
your older brother, CEO Judar Harvey.
My brother has nothing to do with this.
I'm just taking the best course of action
as captain of the Little Garden.
We're heading out, Liddy, Erica.
Right!
Wait, President.
Please take us with you.
Did you not hear what I just said?
I did,
but weren't you the one who told us
about believing in "noblesse oblige"?
However, I believe in noblesse oblige!
Those with power should wield it
for the sake of those without it.
A long time ago,
I was attacked by the Savage
and lost part of my memories.
If we wait for the support team to get there,
the city will just get destroyed.
And so will the lives and
memories of its residents.
I'm not sure what I can do out there,
but I want you to let me go.
Just so you know,
I'm not the one who recommended
that these two go.
It was LiZA.
LiZA did?
She said the best way to reduce casualties and
raise this operation's chances of success
was for Kisaragi Hayato and Emile Crossfode
to sortie along with you three.
Exactly.
Please let us, President.
Please!
I understand.
If that's what LiZA has determined,
I'll have to go along with it.
Variant Awakening
Okay, I'll be going over the operation.
First, Claire-sama, Liddy,
and I will engage the standard
Savage at point alpha.
Once we take it out,
we will engage the Trenta-class
at point gamma.
Kisaragi Hayato and Emile Crossfode
are to move out then.
Please engage the standard
Savage at point beta.
Why don't we all sortie together?
You two have zero experience
out on the field.
We will go out ahead of you and
show you how to fight the Savage.
In any event, once you take out
the Savage at point beta,
your job is done.
We don't need to support you
with the Trenta-class?
Yeah, it looked really strong.
Don't think so lowly of us!
How many Savages do you think
we've eliminated up until this point?
We've also encountered unknowns several times
and have taken them out each time.
Leave the Trenta-class to us.
First we take out the Savage's vision.
Liddy, Erica, let's go!
Right!
Hundred On!
That Hundred...
It's an Arsène type
which creates energy chains that can be
extended or retracted at will.
Its name is Everlasting.
Now, Claire-sama!
Claire is aiming for the Savage's head.
In other words, its core.
Take this!
A Savage's skin is said to be
as strong as steel,
but an attack from a Hundred
can slice through it like butter.
That's the core!
How about I finish you off?
I have to teach those newcomers
not to look down on us!
Pierce through!
Did you see that, Emile Crossfode?!
It's your turn next.
Once you land at the coordinates,
head to beta point immediately—
We can't wait for this thing to land!
The president and the others jumped off,
so we should follow suit.
Right, Hayato?
Hey! You need to hurry up
and deploy your Hundred.
Wh-What is wrong with you?!
Hundred On!
Hayato, let's try to do
the same thing they did.
Huh?
I'll fire some shots to
provide a smokescreen.
Take that chance to attack the core.
Got it.
That's tough.
Hayato!
I know!
I can't get all the way to the core.
This is it.
We did it, Hayato!
Huh?
Yeah.
Liddy!
Leave it to me.
Liddy! Erica!
Let's go save them, Emile!
Yeah.
There's no need for that.
You two stand by there.
I told you the student council
would take care of this one.
But...!
Silence!
I'll destroy you along with the shelter.
One more time...
There's not enough energy?
Is that duel with Kisaragi Hayato
still affecting me?
Claire-sama!
Kisaragi Hayato?!
Are you okay?
I told you to stand by...
There's no way I can just sit there and
watch one of my own get done in.
What's up with your hand?
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Why do you always steal my firsts?
I'm not really trying to...
My first princess carry this time...
That's what you're worried about?!
Claire-sama, you're about to get hit!
This is bad!
Sorry, we'll have to dodge like this.
Wait!
What's going on, Erica?
There's an airport in the direction
the Savage is going to fire.
If you dodge, the people there that are
trying to evacuate will get hit.
President, what should I do?
Put up a barrier and take the blast.
You should be able to do it.
Guess there's no time to hesitate.
We're going to release our energy at
the same time and blow the blast back.
Right.
Let's go!
We did it, Kisaragi Hayato.
It's all thanks to you...
I-It's not like I did it for you.
Oh.
Are you not doing so well?
Yeah, it's taking all my energy
just to keep my armaments on.
That's quite the nice mood
you two have going on there.
E-Emile?
I'm going to talk to you about this later.
Emile!
Emilia!
Are you okay, Emilia?
Hayato?
Wait... Did you remember?
Not all of it,
but I know you're Emilia Hermit.
Hayato...
You saved me again.
We'll talk later.
Emilia, run now.
But...!
Hurry!
Take the vice president for me!
Hayato!
Full-body armament...
It's the same as before...
Hayato....
No, Hayato!
You can't lose yourself!
Vice President!
Are you okay, Erica?
Claire-sama...
Th-Thank you.
Kisaragi Hayato,
just what has gotten into you?
You can't, Hayato!
I guess there's no choice.
Emilia... I...
I'll explain later.
We need to finish him off.
Channel all your energy into your
Flying Swallow and destroy its core.
Can I do it?
You'll be fine now.
Right.
Go!
I did it...
You did it, Hayato.
Yeah.
Emile Crossfode...
Y-You've... got boobs...
And in the middle of combat, you...
You kissed Kisaragi Hayato...
Guess you found me out.
We were able to protect all those people.
And this place.
Isn't that great, Hayato?
Yeah.
We're able to go into combat
because of moments like these.
So you took out the Savage?
It wasn't just me.
The president, Emile,
and everyone else helped.
Anyway, it's unfortunate that
Sakura-san's concert got canceled.
The Savage Appeared on the Zwei Islands,
Resulting In Damage
But I'm glad no one got hurt.
Now you have to make up for worrying me.
Silly.
They told me I can keep pretending to be a guy
since it would get everyone up in arms otherwise.
The president reluctantly agreed.
But...
...I can't stay in this room anymore.
I see.
Emile, I want you to tell me
everything you know.
First, I have to talk about Variants.
Variants?
So basically, because you
were attacked by a Savage,
you got infected with the Savage virus?
That's right.
And since you tried to suck out
my blood to save me, you are as well.
The virus is potent.
Most people die from it.
However, if you're lucky
and you live through it,
your Hundred score goes up incredibly,
and you become extremely compatible.
People like Char call
the infected people Variants.
There aren't even ten of us
in the entire world.
So I knew I'd be able to see you again.
I had Char checking the Hundred tests
throughout the world.
So that's why you knew I'd be coming here,
and came to the Little Garden yourself.
I didn't think I'd be coming to the Warslarn school
that Char was assigned to, though.
But why did you have to pretend to be a guy?
Well...
...I wanted to be in the same room as you.
That's not the only reason, though.
It'd be bad if people found out.
Well, you can tell me about that later.
So, the reason I lose my memories
in the middle of a battle
is because I'm a Variant?
Yeah. When you're in danger of dying,
the virus activates, you lose yourself,
and go on a rampage.
It's one of the characteristics
of being a Variant.
Then you too, Emile...
But I've learned to control it with training.
I wonder if I'll be able to do it, too.
It'll be fine.
You'll be able to control it
if you undergo training.
Let's do our best together.
Yeah. Thanks.
Hey, Hayato...
Hm?
That day in Gudenberg, and today...
I want to thank you for saving me.
I've always wanted to thank you.
Oh, yeah.
I need to make some tea.
I'll do it.
H-Hayato...
If you give me a little more time,
I wouldn't mind...
Th-That's not it.
My body just...
Wait. Could this be a side effect
of the virus activating?
H-Hey.
In order to suppress an activated virus,
you need to administer an inactive virus.
In other words, I just administered mine.
Do you...
...not like kissing me?
N-No, that's not it,
but...
Emile Crossfode!
I told you to move rooms immediately!
P-President?!
Wh-Wh-What are you two doing?!
A-And you're on top of each other...
No, we were just...!
H-Hey, what are you doing?!
I-I'm sorry!
You took another one of my "firsts"...
Th-That was an accident! An accident!
I know that.
You don't have to apologize.
You know, you're being
strangely nice to Hayato.
You've been kind of weird since yesterday.
Th-That's totally not true.
Then why did you come here?!
I wanted to make sure you left the room.
It's my job, as student council president.
If something bad happened, you know...
Something bad?
You kissed Hayato yourself!
Hayato, kiss me again!
I can't lose to the president!
Stop it, Emile Crossfode!
Kisaragi Hayato, you too!
And why do you have a problem
with Hayato and me kissing?
Too bad about the concert.
Yeah...
It's good no one was hurt, though.
We'll have another chance.
You can come to delight people
with your song then.
Yeah.
A video of the hero Slayer
that saved the Zwei Islands...
Hero...
Bodyguard